    { question: "What is the goal of Getom?", options: ["Digital solutions", "Next-gen digital tech solutions", "Banking", "Next-gen tech solutions"], answer: "Next-gen digital tech solutions" },
    { question: "Which is a Getom subsidiary?", options: ["gethome", "Hicode", "Hi-Dev", "getomhello"], answer: "Hi-Dev" },
    { question: "Nigeria's capital is?", options: ["Abuja", "Lagos", "Port Harcourt", "Kano"], answer: "Abuja" },
    { question: "Which year did Nigeria gain independence?", options: ["1960", "1970", "1950", "1963"], answer: "1960" },
    { question: "What does GetRecharged offer?", options: ["Airtime and data desale", "Airtime and data for mobile", "Airtime and data resale", "battery increase"], answer: "Airtime and data resale" },
    { question: "Which is a not a Getom subsidiary?", options: ["Hi-dev", "Hi-design", "Getconnected", "Getomhello"], answer: "Getomhello" },
    { question: "What is Getom's focus?", options: ["Digital de-solutions", "Digital solutions", "Non-Digital Solutions", "Solutions for all"], answer: "Digital solutions" },
    { question: "Which continent is Getom in?", options: ["Korea", "Asia", "Africa", "Australia"], answer: "Africa" },
    { question: "Getom's graphics design arm is?", options: ["Hi-Design", "Hi-designbygetom", "Hi-deign", "Hi-degin"], answer: "Hi-Design" },
    { question: "Who founded Getom?", options: ["you", "Oladosu Goodness", "Goodness Oladosu", "Goodness Emmanel Oladosu"], answer: "Goodness Oladosu" },